Finding Aid for Robert Kalmbach photograph collection, 1960-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives and Contact Sheets
  - U-M Baseball photos
    - 1986
      - Grand Valley State 3/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Cleveland State 4/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Toledo 4/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Western Michigan 4/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Indiana State 5/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Michigan State 5/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Ohio State 5/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Wayne State 5/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
    - 1987
      - Adrian 4/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Cleveland State 4/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Purdue 4/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Wayne State 4/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Indiana 5/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Michigan State 5/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Big Tens 5/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
    - 1988
      - Western Michigan 3/30/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Minnesota 4/09/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Ferris State 4/12/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Eastern Michigan 4/13/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Michigan State 4/20/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Wisconsin 5/01/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Ohio State 5/07/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Big Tens 5/19/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
    - 1989
      - Eastern Michigan 3/25/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Northwestern 4/01/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Purdue 4/15/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Siena Heights 4/23/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Michigan State 5/05/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Big Tens 5/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
    - 1990
      - Western Michigan 3/28/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Iowa 4/08/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Minnesota 4/14/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
      - Ohio State 5/13/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 28)
    - 1991
      - Eastern Michigan 3/23/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Detroit 4/04/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Illinois 4/13/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Purdue 4/20/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Hillsdale 4/25/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Indiana 5/04/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
    - 1992
      - Detroit 4/08/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Minnesota 4/11/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Siena Heights 4/14/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Ohio State 5/03/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Penn State 5/10/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
    - 1993
      - Indiana 4/18/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Ferris State 4/24/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Western Michigan 5/04/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Northwestern 5/08/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Michigan State 5/16/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
    - 1996
      - Oakland 3/28/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Minnesota 4/06/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Hillsdale 4/10/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Penn State 4/20-21/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Siena Heights 4/29/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
    - 1997
      - Western Michigan 3/26/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Penn State 3/29-30/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Northwestern 4/11-12/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Siena Heights 4/27/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Eastern Michigan 5/01/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Toledo 5/07/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Ohio State 5/10/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Illinois 5/17/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
    - 1998
      - Oakland 4/08/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Minnesota 4/10-12/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Michigan State 4/17/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Michigan State 4/19/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Central Michigan 4/30/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Penn State, 5/1-3/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Eastern Michigan 5/06/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 29)
      - Reunion 1953 NCAA Champs, 9/20/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
    - 1999
      - Central Michigan 3/30/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Illinois 4/03/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Eastern Michigan 4/07/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Ohio State 4/10/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Indiana 5/8-10/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Eastern Michigan 5/11/1999 (Box 30)
    - 2000
      - Minnesota 3/25/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Siena Heights 4/23/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan State, 5/5-7/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Central Michigan 5/10/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Iowa 5/13-14/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
  - U-M Hockey photos
    - 1970-1971
      - Pioneer basketball, Michigan hockey 3/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
    - 1971-1972
      - Hockey 12/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Hockey 1/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan State 2/09/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
    - 1972-1973
      - Hockey, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
    - 1973-1974
      - Waterloo 11/02/1973, negatives (Box 30)
      - Wisconsin 11/23-24/1973, negatives (Box 30)
      - Notre Dame, 12/7-8/1973, negatives (Box 30)
      - Minnesota 1/25-26/1974, negatives (Box 30)
      - Minnesota 1/25-26/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan Tech 2/8-9/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan State 3/1-2/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Toronto area hockey players, Michigan area hockey players, Don Dufek, negatives (Box 30)
    - 1974-1975
      - Ohio State 10/25-26/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Wisconsin, 11/1-2/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan Tech 11/22-23/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Colorado 11/29-30/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan State 12/13-14/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Notre Dame, 1/3-4/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Minnesota 1/24-25/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan State 2/28-3/01/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
    - 1975-1976
      - USA Olympic team 11/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - North Dakota 11/7-8/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan Tech 11/21-22/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Michigan State, 12/5-6/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Czechoslovakia 1/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Minnesota-Duluth, 1/9-10/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Notre Dame 1/16-17/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Minnesota 1/23-24/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 30)
      - Bowling Green 2/03/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Denver 2/13-14/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Wisconsin 2/20-21/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan State, 3/5-6/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Notre Dame 3/10-11/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
    - 1976-1977
      - Minnesota 11/06/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Minnesota-Duluth, 12/3-4/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan State 12/10-11/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Colorado 1/7-8/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan Tech 1/14-15/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Wisconsin 2/4-5/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Denver 2/11-12/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan State 3/4-5/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan Tech 3/9-10/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Denver 3/13/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Boston 3/24/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Wisconsin 3/26/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
    - 1977-1978
      - Bowling Green 10/21-22/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Denver 10/28-29/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan State 11/11-12/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Minnesota 11/18-19/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Wisconsin 12/2-3/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - North Dakota 1/20-21/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Notre Dame 2/3-4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan Tech 2/24-25/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan State 3/3-4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
    - 1978-1979
      - Minnesota-Duluth 10/27-28/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Denver 11/17-18/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Michigan State 12/8-9/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Ohio State 12/29/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Boston vs. Michigan Tech 12/29/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Minnesota 1/5-6/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Colorado 1/12-13/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 31)
      - Dekers Hall of Fame inductees 2/1979, negatives (Box 31)
    - 1979-1980
      - Minnesota-Duluth 10/26-27/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Minnesota 1/2-3/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Dartmouth 12/7-8/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Boston 1/04/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Princeton 1/05/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Colorado 1/11-12/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Poland 2/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Notre Dame 2/15-16/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 32)
      - Michigan State 2/29-3/01/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 32)
    - 1980-1981
      - Western Michigan 10/24-25/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - North Dakota, 12/5-6/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 32)
      - Toronto 12/12-13/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Michigan State 1/16-17/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Denver 2/20-21/1981, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 32)
      - Michigan Tech 2/27-28/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
    - 1981-1982
      - Toronto 10/30-31/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Michigan State 11/20-21/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Ohio State, 12/4-5/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Northern Michigan 12/19-20/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Michigan State 1/18/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Chicago Circle 1/22-23/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Michigan Tech, 2/5-6/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Miami 2/12-13/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
    - 1982-1983
      - Windsor 10/15-16/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Ohio State 11/19-20/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Northern Michigan 11/26-27/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Western Michigan 12/3-4/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Ferris State 12/10-11/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Notre Dame 12/29/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 32)
      - Illinois-Chicago, 1/7-8/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan State 1/28-29/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan Tech 2/25-26/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
    - 1983-1984
      - Miami 10/28-29/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - New Hampshire, 11/4-5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan State 11/18-19/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Lake Superior 12/2-3/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Ferris State 12/9-10/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Bowling Green, 1/6-7/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan State 1/27-28/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Ferris State 2/10-11/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan Tech 2/17-18/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
    - 1984-1985
      - Ferris State 10/19-20/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Bowling Green 10/26-27/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan State, 11/9-10/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Lake Superior 11/23-24/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Ohio State 11/30-12/01/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Japan 12/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Western Michigan 12/7-8/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Miami 12/14-15/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Russia 1/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Ferris State 1/4-5/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Bowling Green 1/11-12/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan State 1/25-26/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Western Michigan 2/22-23/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
    - 1985-1986
      - Miami 10/11-12/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Bowling Green 10/25-26/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan State, 11/8-9/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Czechoslovakia 12/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Western Michigan 12/6-7/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - RPI 1/17-18/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Lake Superior 2/07/1986, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Ohio State 2/14-15/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Western Michigan 2/21-22/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
    - 1986-1987
      - Bowling Green 10/10-11/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Ferris State 11/7-8/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Michigan State 11/14-15/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
      - Lake Superior 11/28-29/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 33)
    - 1986-1987
      - Miami 12/12-13/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Illinois-Chicago, 1/9-10/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Michigan 1/30-31/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Lake Superior 2/07/1986, contact sheet only (Box 34)
      - Alaska-Fairbanks 2/13-14/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Bowling Green 2/20-21/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
    - 1987-1988
      - Illinois-Chicago 10/30-31/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Michigan State 11/13-14/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Michigan 11/20-21/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Boston, 12/4-5/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Miami 12/11-12/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Ohio State, 1/8-9/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Michigan, 2/5-6/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Lake Superior 2/12-13/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
    - 1988-1989
      - Illinois-Chicago 10/21/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Bowling Green 11/4-5/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Ohio State 11/18-19/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Michigan State 12/9-11/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Ferris State 1/20-21/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Notre Dame 2/10-11/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Michigan State 2/17-18/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Bowling Green 3/3-5/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
    - 1989-1990
      - Western Ontario 10/17/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Ferris State 11/10-11/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Michigan 11/24-25/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Boston 12/1-2/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Michigan State, 12/9-10/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Illinois-Chicago 12/15-16/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Bowling Green 1/12-13/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Ohio State 1/26-27/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Michigan 2/2-3/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Alaska 2/9-10/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Miami 2/23-24/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Michigan 3/2-3/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
    - 1990-1991
      - Bowling Green 10/18-19/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Ontario 10/21/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Illinois-Chicago 10/26-27/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Michigan State, 11/9-10/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Ohio State 11/23-24/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Western Michigan, 12/7-8/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Lake Superior State 12/14-15/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Miami 1/11-12/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 34)
      - Kent State 2/22/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ohio State 3/1-2/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ferris State 3/08/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Dekers 1991 Hall of Fame inductees, 1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
    - 1991-1992
      - Michigan State 10/25-26/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Western Michigan, 11/1-2/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Minnesota, 11/8-9/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ohio State 11/19/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ferris State, 1/3-4/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Notre Dame 1/10-11/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ohio State 1/24-25/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Lake Superior State 1/31-2/01/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Bowling Green 2/7-8/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Dekers Hall of Fame 2/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Bowling Green 3/03/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ohio State 3/13-14/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Northern Michigan 3/29/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
    - 1992-1993
      - Notre Dame 10/17/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Miami 11/13-14/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Western Michigan 11/27/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Michigan State 12/4-5/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Kent State 12/11-12/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Bowling Green 1/16/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Lake Superior State 2/26/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
    - 1993-1994
      - Ohio State 11/19-20/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Western Michigan 12/3-4/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Illinois-Chicago 12/17-18/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Lake Superior State, 1/7-8/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Bowling Green 1/25/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Kent State 3/11-12/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
    - 1994-1995
      - Colorado 10/21-22/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ohio State 11/04/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Michigan State 11/11/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Notre Dame 12/03/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Bowling Green 1/20/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Illinois-Chicago 1/28/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Western Michigan 2/03/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
      - Ohio State 3/10-11/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 35)
    - 1995-1996
      - Western Michigan 10/20/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Alaska 11/18/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
    - 1995-1996
      - Ferris State 1/05/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Miami 1/06/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Ohio State 2/03/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Miami 3/08/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
    - 1996-1997
      - Waterloo 10/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Brown 11/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Ohio State 11/08/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Bowling Green 11/09/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Michigan State 11/15/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Western Michigan 12/04/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Michigan Tech 12/27/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Lake Superior State 12/29/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Cornell 1/07/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Western Michigan 1/18/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Miami 1/25/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Bowling Green 2/01/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Notre Dame 2/15/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Lake Superior State 2/22/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Michigan State 3/01/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Bowling Green 3/02/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Alaska 3/08/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - CCHA Final 3/15/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Players watching NCAA 3/16/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Minnesota 3/23/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
    - 1997-1998
      - Toronto 10/12/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Michigan State 10/25/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Minnesota 11/28/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Wisconsin 11/30/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - GLI 12/27-28/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Ohio State 1/02/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Bowling Green 1/09/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Miami 2/13/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Northern Michigan 2/14/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 36)
      - Michigan State 2/21/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Lake Superior State 2/28/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Notre Dame 3/14/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Notre Dame 3/15/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - NCAA Regionals (Princeton/North Dakota) 3/27-28/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
    - 1998-1999
      - Old-Timers' game 8/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Stanley Cup in locker room 9/24/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Lake Superior State 10/11/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Niagara 10/17/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Bowling Green 10/30/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Michigan State 11/20/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - GLI, Michigan Tech/Michigan State 12/26-27/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Ferris State, 1/8-9/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)